hittail.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | HitTail

  1. Home
  2. Privacy Policy

Effective: January 27, 2016

HitTail Inc., d/b/a HitTail (HitTail) understands how important the privacy of personal information is to its users. This Privacy Policy will tell you the minimal information that is collected through your use of this website. It will explain the choices you have about how your personal information is used and how we protect that information. It will also explain the security of the information we collect on your behalf when you register for a HitTail account.

HitTail contains links to other sites. Once you enter another website, please be aware that HitTail is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. The only information we normally collect will be non-personal information through the use of cookies or web beacons (explained below). Non-personal information is defined as data that is not traceable back to any individual and cannot be used to identify an individual, e.g. the keyword phrase you searched on to find this website. However, if you choose to contact us, then you will be submitting personally identifiable information in the form of your name and email address along with anything else you volunteer.

NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

In general, you can browse HitTail without giving us any personal information. We use HitTail to analyze traffic to our website in order to understand our customer and visitors needs and to continually improve our site for them. HitTail collects only anonymous, aggregate statistics. For example, we do not tie a specific visit to a specific visitor.

See the next section for more regarding the personal information that you voluntarily send to us.

A. Cookies

What is a cookie? A cookie is a small data file that is stored on the hard drive of the computer you use to view a website. Cookies placed by HitTail are session based non-persistent cookies and can only be read by HitTail and any network or maintenance contractors working on our behalf (as described below).

Cookies placed by HitTail for web surfers contain non-personally identifiable information and are deleted when you close your web browser. We collect non-personal information about your use of our website as a web surfer. Every computer that accesses HitTail is assigned a different cookie that allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using the website. We also may use cookie information to determine the popularity of certain content. Most web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Opera, and Apple Safari can be set to reject all cookies and offer instructions on how to do so in the "Help" section of the toolbar. Rejecting cookies will not impede browsing of [https://www.hittail.com](https://www.hittail.com/) as a visitor in any way.

Cookies placed by HitTail for registered users and subscribers contain potentially personally identifiable information (your username and URL) but they are deleted when you close the browser or log out of the HitTail service. These cookies are required to create an account, subscribe, and use the HitTail services.

B. Web Beacons

Web beacons are tiny graphic image files, imbedded in a webpage in GIF, PNG, JPEG or HTML format, that provide a presence on the webpage and send back to its home server (which can belong to the HitTail or a website contractor) information from the Users' browser, such as the IP address, the URL of the page on which the beacon is located, the type browser that is accessing the site and the ID number of any cookies on the users' computer previously placed by that server. Web beacons can also be used to place a cookie on the users' browser. Web beacons may also be known as clear GIFs, web bugs, 1-by-1 GIFs, single-pixel GIFs, 1x1 pixels, or clear pixels.

We may use web beacons to collect non-personal information about your use of our website. The information collected by web beacons allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using our website. Our web beacons are not used to track your activity outside of HitTail. We do not link non-personal information from web beacons to personally identifiable information you have volunteered without your permission.

VOLUNTEERING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

This Privacy Policy does not apply to content, business information, ideas, concepts or inventions that you send to HitTail by email, forum post, or blog comment. If you want to keep content or business information, ideas, concepts or inventions private or proprietary, do not send them in an email to us or post them to our forum.

A. Emails You Send to HitTail

When you contact HitTail, you are providing us with at minimum your email address. You may optionally provide us with additional information such as your real name or the company you represent. HitTail will keep this information in confidence and not share it with third parties. You will not be added to mailing lists unless requested.

B. Commenting on the HitTail Blog

When you comment on the HitTail blog, you must fill out your name and e-mail or log in with your WordPress username instead, so please keep this in mind when commenting. Please see WordPress’ privacy policies for more information on their systems at <https://wordpress.org/about/privacy/>

C. Registering for the HitTail Forum

When you create an account on the HitTail forum and/or post to the forum, you can choose to do so with an anonymous username. If you choose to reveal your real name, please realize this is a public forum.

D. Signing up for a HitTail Basic Low Volume Account

When you create a free HitTail account, you must provide us with a username, email address, and URL. This is the minimum information needed for us to provide the HitTail service. When you create an account, you can optionally provide us with additional information such as your real name, company, or title. Registering an account with this data is done through secure sockets layer technology (SSL). SSL is a proven secure communication protocol that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

HitTail processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

E. Subscribing to a HitTail Basic High Volume, Plus or Premium Account

When you subscribe to a HitTail Basic High Volume, HitTail Plus or HitTail Premium, you must provide us with a username, email address, and URL and in the case of HitTail Premium your Google AdWords login username and password. This is the minimum information needed for us to provide the selected HitTail service. When you create an account, you can optionally provide us with additional information such as your real name, company, or title. Registering an account with this data is done through secure sockets layer technology (SSL). SSL is a proven secure communication protocol that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Under no circumstances will we hold sensitive payment details such as your credit card number, expiration date or security code. All transactions are handled through one of our accredited payment bureaus, PayPal or Stripe. All communication between HitTail and PayPal/Stripe occur through secure sockets layer technology (SSL). SSL is a proven secure communication protocol that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. For more information on PayPal's privacy policy please refer to <https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>. For more information on Stripe's privacy policy please refer to: <https://stripe.com/us/privacy>

F. Subscribing to a HitTail Personal, Pro, Business, or Agency Account

When you subscribe to a HitTail Personal, Pro, Business, or Agency account, you must provide us with a username, email address, and URL. This is the minimum information needed for us to provide the selected HitTail service. When you create an account, you can optionally provide us with additional information such as your real name, company, or title. Registering an account with this data is done through secure sockets layer technology (SSL). SSL is a proven secure communication protocol that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Under no circumstances will we hold sensitive payment details such as your credit card number, expiration date or security code. All transactions are handled through one of our accredited payment bureaus, PayPal or Stripe. All communication between HitTail and PayPal/Stripe occur through secure sockets layer technology (SSL). SSL is a proven secure communication protocol that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. For more information on PayPal's privacy policy please refer to <https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>. For more information on Stripe's privacy policy please refer to: <https://stripe.com/us/privacy>

SECURITY OF YOUR FINANCIAL INFORMATION

DO NOT SEND US YOUR CREDIT CARD NUMBER THROUGH EMAIL, POST IT TO THE HITTAIL FORUM OR AS A COMMENT IN THE HITTAIL BLOG.

We cannot be held accountable for the security of your information sent through email, posted to the forum or the blog. We will not ask for your financial information through email, in the forum, or on the blog. The only place you should enter this information is through PayPal. For more information on PayPal's accredited security procedures, please refer to <https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>.

SECURITY OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT ON YOUR BEHALF

At no time will the contents of your information collected on your behalf by subscribing for a HitTail account be shared with third parties. HitTail does not use any content collected and stored on your behalf. The totality of information collected on your behalf (e.g. the total number of website visits tracked by HitTail, or the number of keyword transfers into your Google Adwords account) will be monitored by HitTail so that we can bill you according to the amount of resources required by your use of the HitTail service.

HitTail may provide aggregate quantitative data to third parties, including but not limited to the number of users of the HitTail service, the number of search hits recorded by HitTail, the number of keywords collected, the number of suggestions delivered, or the averages of HitTail users thereof. Please see below for more information on aggregate data.

SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us and information collected on your behalf, both during transmission and once we receive it. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

By using HitTail, you acknowledge and agree that HitTail may access, preserve, and disclose your account information and any information associated with that account if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (b) protect property or defend or assert legal rights in special cases, such as in response to a physical threat to you or others, (b) enforce our Terms of Use Policy, including investigation of potential violations hereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues (including, without limitation, the filtering of spam), (d) respond to user support requests, or (e) protect the rights, property or safety of HitTail, its users and the public. HitTail will not be responsible or liable for the exercise or non-exercise of its rights under the Terms of Service.

In the event that we are legally compelled to disclose this information to a third party, we will attempt to notify you unless doing so would violate the law or court order.

In addition, we may disclose personal information as described below.

A. Disclosure to Network and Maintenance Contractors

People working on our behalf to maintain the website may sometimes have limited access to your username, email address, and URL in the course of providing products or services to HitTail. These contractors include vendors and suppliers that provide us with technology, services, and/or content for the operation and maintenance of our website. Unless you notify us otherwise, these contractors also may have access to any additional information you provided to us such as your real name, company, and title in the course of their testing. The only personally identifiable information accessible to these contractors is the minimum required to create an account (your username, email address, and URL). This is the minimum necessary for the contractor to perform their limited functions for HitTail. We also contractually require that our operations and maintenance contractors (1) protect the privacy of your email address consistent with this Privacy Policy, and (2) not use or disclose it for any purpose other than providing us with products and services as required by law.

B. Disclosure of Aggregate Information

HitTail may provide general aggregate information to third parties. This sort of statistical data is called aggregate information because it reflects the habits and characteristics of a large group of anonymous people. Websites may use aggregate data or share it with their business partners so that the information and services they provide best meet the needs of the users.

We require parties with whom we share aggregate information to agree that they will not attempt to make this information personally identifiable in any way, such as by combining it with other databases.

PROTECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Despite HitTail's best efforts to protect your information while using our website, there is always some risk that an unauthorized third party may find a way around our security systems or that transmissions of your information over the Internet may be intercepted.

HitTail processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

PRIVACY OF CHILDREN

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. HitTail is not designed for or intended to attract children under the age of 13. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13. Children's parents or guardians are solely responsible for providing supervision of any of their children's use of this website.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

HitTail will keep the most up-to-date policy on this page accessible at <https://www.hittail.com/privacy>. Any material changes in the way HitTail uses personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Policy, with the date of those changes clearly noted on the first page. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Please exit the site immediately if you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any future revised policy.

SERVICE-RELATED ANNOUNCEMENTS

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by contacting [service@hittail.com](mailto:service@hittail.com).

CUSTOMER SERVICE

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us when contacting us, joining the HitTail forum, or creating a HitTail service account, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. PayPal and Stripe may also send you emails as receipt for your payment if you subscribe for a HitTail service. PayPal and Stripe may also notify you of any changes made to your subscription, including account upgrades, downgrades, and/or cancellation. You can read PayPal’s privacy policy at <https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>, and Stripe’s privacy policy at: <https://stripe.com/us/privacy>

CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions regarding these Terms of Use, please contact HitTail at [service@hittail.com](mailto:service@hittail.com).

View [Terms of Service](http://www.hittail.com/terms).
